

# CONTACT

≥ benaoun.hazem@aiesec.net

+216-24-219-704

Skaness,Monastir,Tunisia

# **Ben Aoun Hazem**

Computer Science Student

### **PROFILE**

Computer science student in faculty of science of Monastir. Experienced with all stages of volunteering work cycle for making positive impact in society. Learned numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, C, C++, C#, Python, Java.

#### **EDUCATION**

Faculty of Sciences of Monastir
 Bachelor of Computer Science
 -Present

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Advanced
Passed TOEFL ITP 500pts

- French
  Intermidiate
- SpanishBeginner
- ArabicNative

# **SKILL**

- Web Design(Js/HTML5/CSS/Bootstrap)
- Programming(C/C++/C#/Java/Python)
- Front End Coding
- Leadership
- Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools(Trello/JIRA)
- Team communication Tools
- Agile Method Implementation

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2022 - 2023

# **International Relations Manager**

AIESEC in SWEDEN

International Relations Manager in national board: I establish international relations with other entities of AIESEC (we provide Leadership opportunities for youth through exchange.

2022 - 2023

#### **Data & Process Manager**

AIESEC in TUNISIA

Process Hacker Manager in national board: I created Tools and Sheets to organize and facilitate the International Incoming global volunteer department (we provide Leadership opportunities to international youth in Tunisia).

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

2018 – 202

#### **Treasurer**

JCI Junior Medenine

JUNIOR Treasurer 2020 : Developing Youth Leadership skills and empowering other new members to do a positive impact in our society.

2018 – 2019

## **Ambassador Of Peace**

UNICRI Project (Voices of Peace)

Human Resources &Data Manager on the International level :VOP project aims to prevent and mitigate a phenomenon that affects the Tunisian society The rise of violence and extremism .

2022

#### Organizing committee Sales Vice president of ROOTs:

**AIESEC** in Monastir

Roots is a yearly conference that prepares new AIESECers for their new experience by giving them the needed knowledge, motivating them to take the lead, encouraging them to be a global citizen that aims to help the world and to fulfil peace and to work on the AIESEC values that are aligned with sustainable development goals.